My role is to always remain embedded in the truth.
My role is to be a consummate skeptic until proven otherwise.
I will always be the person at the party that says, now hold on now.
I literally get invited to parties in order to be the person who says, now hold on now.
Now, so though you want me to be excited about things like Zoran standing next to Trump and saying, you know, Israel's having a genocide, I will not.
Because again, it is words.
He was literally allowed to say that.
And whenever you are doing something you are allowed to do, you're not really doing the thing.
So when you say that, at the same time as allowing the New York City Police Department to be headed by a consummate Zionist who put forth violent repression against peaceful protesters of a genocide, your actions are louder than words.
I have been a card-carrying member of the International Thespian Society since 1995.
I know theater when I see it.
Y'all can be hype.
I will remain critical.
Support a real one.